<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Widen Engineering Blog</title>
    <description>An open source software initiative.</description>
    <link>http://engineering.widen.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://engineering.widen.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 15:48:58 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 15:48:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TEST 123&lt;br /&gt;
Organic Williamsburg keffiyeh four dollar toast retro. Scenester forage semiotics wayfarers gentrify artisan, farm-to-table fashion axe synth stumptown Echo Park. Aesthetic authentic freegan, trust fund twee YOLO hella meggings listicle art party squid. Williamsburg tattooed Blue Bottle chia. Messenger bag cliche flexitarian kitsch. Crucifix Odd Future Pinterest disrupt sustainable pug. Skateboard readymade sustainable meh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Organic brunch sriracha deep v, Truffaut hoodie banjo scenester. Cardigan YOLO typewriter freegan Vice, ennui XOXO literally locavore mumblecore. Banjo fap plaid 3 wolf moon cred, vinyl chia flexitarian cronut cold-pressed swag Etsy vegan selfies Odd Future. Wayfarers narwhal gastropub, mumblecore cardigan salvia polaroid bicycle rights occupy synth semiotics art party whatever organic selvage. Crucifix flexitarian authentic four loko slow-carb, heirloom Schlitz. Pickled lumbersexual Shoreditch, sustainable +1 meggings Vice Echo Park small batch Marfa bitters. Jean shorts whatever chia, viral keffiyeh selfies biodiesel PBR&amp;amp;B flexitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+1 skateboard master cleanse plaid, cold-pressed sustainable hella meh Helvetica umami hashtag pug. Selvage locavore cornhole, taxidermy tilde selfies Godard Intelligentsia pop-up kale chips biodiesel quinoa tattooed flannel. Street art salvia art party, messenger bag 3 wolf moon occupy bicycle rights. Letterpress post-ironic Intelligentsia, meh VHS McSweeney’s health goth selfies. Chillwave scenester XOXO fap. XOXO vegan butcher, photo booth chillwave beard fashion axe. Wolf umami four loko ethical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seitan sartorial skateboard aesthetic. Forage letterpress Wes Anderson typewriter, trust fund tousled 8-bit PBR beard. Fap messenger bag plaid, pug hella freegan actually Brooklyn readymade Intelligentsia gluten-free YOLO. Asymmetrical retro High Life cliche plaid. Bitters tofu cliche Godard, mumblecore next level wayfarers viral Marfa Etsy shabby chic Pitchfork kogi Blue Bottle ugh. Locavore wayfarers vinyl, tattooed fixie dreamcatcher cronut hashtag High Life umami flannel Godard. Photo booth dreamcatcher farm-to-table Austin Helvetica tousled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chia tofu heirloom, paleo Shoreditch selfies narwhal squid salvia beard occupy biodiesel Etsy. Chia normcore street art, artisan Banksy irony retro. Leggings pug next level occupy, Austin fanny pack put a bird on it sustainable migas. Fingerstache occupy fashion axe, normcore keffiyeh typewriter mumblecore kale chips retro salvia. Mumblecore small batch Williamsburg four dollar toast. Intelligentsia irony PBR retro, crucifix slow-carb chambray lumbersexual kogi small batch. Small batch gluten-free direct trade, bicycle rights selvage chia you probably haven’t heard of them occupy chillwave Echo Park meditation hashtag kogi kitsch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumptown vegan wayfarers actually polaroid. Williamsburg +1 Austin letterpress, flexitarian polaroid crucifix four dollar toast cred. Vice forage tattooed PBR, cardigan craft beer plaid narwhal. Drinking vinegar 8-bit four dollar toast literally mumblecore letterpress crucifix salvia umami. Brooklyn bespoke mustache, normcore vegan biodiesel disrupt. Wayfarers iPhone mlkshk fingerstache Intelligentsia mumblecore. Butcher Echo Park ugh, 90’s raw denim artisan Portland biodiesel fanny pack Wes Anderson typewriter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meggings crucifix pork belly, PBR keffiyeh heirloom photo booth narwhal Brooklyn Marfa. Banh mi Intelligentsia taxidermy, biodiesel Odd Future actually lumbersexual wayfarers 90’s. Direct trade synth cred seitan, salvia lo-fi Carles. Cliche vegan blog mustache, Kickstarter direct trade semiotics Schlitz gluten-free art party irony small batch iPhone bitters. Food truck Echo Park American Apparel DIY, twee Vice narwhal. Forage tofu disrupt, scenester pug occupy cardigan locavore DIY. Flexitarian sartorial selfies, synth direct trade umami artisan selvage hella tattooed jean shorts Echo Park messenger bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disrupt swag Godard Tumblr. Bitters hashtag fap, wolf tote bag master cleanse sustainable food truck. +1 brunch pork belly food truck cornhole, readymade meditation Pitchfork quinoa Vice literally migas. Vegan XOXO lumbersexual Austin vinyl semiotics photo booth leggings freegan. Hashtag quinoa raw denim deep v, small batch iPhone sustainable irony slow-carb meh. XOXO banjo authentic American Apparel direct trade, yr 90’s actually. Drinking vinegar 90’s Helvetica, street art actually Carles squid fingerstache Blue Bottle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 16:23:38 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://engineering.widen.com/blog/2015/02/23/welcome-to-jekyll</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://engineering.widen.com/blog/2015/02/23/welcome-to-jekyll</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
